http://www.mrsstewart.com/policies/privacy-policy

Skip to Content
Welcome to our store!
Brighten Swimming Pool Water
Brighten Fish Bait! (Yes, really!)
My shopping cart
Your cart is currently empty.
Brighten Swimming Pool Water
Brighten Fish Bait! (Yes, really!)
Menu is closed
Happy Thanksgiving!
Mrs Stewart's Bluing will be closed from November 26-29 for the Thanksgiving Day holiday. Stay safe and warm!
Privacy policy
This Privacy Policy pertains to any personal information (name, address, phone, email) and, where noted, any credit card information we may obtain from you during the process of online account set up at our website, account set up with our company, or product purchase from us via purchase order, phone, fax, email or website shopping cart.
To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed. We do our best to treat your information as we would like our information to be treated - carefully.
Here are some details regarding how we handle your personal information:
Shopify Our website is hosted on Shopify Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you. Your personal information and credit card information is stored through Shopify’s data storage, databases and the general Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall. We are not responsible for Shopify’s practices.
Shopify Payment Gateway When placing an order at our website, if you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.
All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.
PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.
We encourage you to read Shopify’s Terms of Service (https://www.shopify.com/legal/terms) or Privacy Statement (https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy). We encourage you to review their information via these links often as the information at Shopify may have change, rendering some of the above information obsolete. We will review these thinks often and change this policy as necessary or when updates are received from Shopify.
Other than Shopify
Non Website Credit Card Purchases The computer / data systems on location at Jefco, Inc. dba Mrs. Stewart’s Bluing are PCI compliant. We do not store electronic credit card information on location in our systems. All credit card processing for orders placed at our website and otherwise (fax, email, phone) are processed through the Shopify Payment Gateway system, ensuring proper credit card encryption for all credit card processing, website related and non-website related.
How we use your Personal Information With one exception, we will NEVER EVER give, sell or distribute your personal information to anyone. The one exception would be that we may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service. We have access on location only to your personal information (name, address, phone, email). We do not have access on location to your credit card information. If required by law, we would release your personal information to legal authorities only. Release of your credit card information would be governed by Shopify and Shopify Payment policies.
We gather your personal information when you place an order with us. This information is used to connect with you regarding your order. This information is also used to connect with you promotionally (coupon offers, newsletter, blog, etc.) regarding the Jefco, Inc. dba Mrs. Stewart’s Bluing line of products. When setting up an account or placing an order with us at our website, you may opt-in or opt-out of various communications from us and we will abide by your choices. You may go into your online account with us at any time to change any of these settings.
We may set up a customer account for you in our systems on location at Jefco, Inc. dba Mrs. Stewart’s Bluing. Again, this does not include credit card information. It may include name, address, phone, email and order history.
We cannot protect your personal information under these circumstances: Jefco, Inc. dba Mrs. Stewart’s Bluing will not be held liable to our Privacy Policy when you place and order via an online store such as Amazon, Ebay or any similar venue. We do not sell our products directly on these stores. We have no control over how these stores or the sellers represented on these stores handle both your personal information and your credit card information. We recommend, when purchasing from these stores, that you review both the store Privacy Policy, Terms of Service, etc. and the Sellers Privacy Policy, Terms of Service, etc. before purchasing through them.
Jefco, Inc. dba Mrs Stewart’s Bluing will not be held liable to our Privacy Policy when you connect with us via social media, that is, when you “Follow” us on Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, and other similar venues as we do not have control over how you yourself set your notification preferences on these venues, nor do we have control over how these venues use your personal information. Again, before using these venues, we encourage you to review their Privacy Policy and Terms of Services to better understand how they may handle your personal information.
Jefco, Inc. dba Mrs. Stewart’s Bluing will not be held liable to our Privacy Policy once you leave our website via any of our links that take you away from our website. Once you leave our website, you are then governed under the policies of the website where you arrive.
If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please Contact Us.
